<xt:extension xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension" id="com.oxygenxml.resources.batch.converter.plugin">
    <xt:location href="${project.build.finalName}-plugin.jar"/>
    <xt:version>${project.nosnapshot.version}</xt:version>
    <xt:oxy_version>26.0+</xt:oxy_version>
    <xt:type>plugin</xt:type>
    <xt:author>Syncro Soft</xt:author>
    <xt:name>Batch Documents Converter</xt:name>
    <xt:description><html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
            <head>
                <title>Oxygen resources converter</title>
            </head>
            <body>
                <div>
                    <p>This add-on contributes actions in the Tools menu and contextual menu to
                        enable batch conversion between various formats: </p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Word to XHTML/DITA/DocBook</li>
                        <li>HTML to XHTML/DITA/DocBook</li>
                        <li>Markdown to XHTML/DITA/DocBook</li>
                        <li>Excel to DITA</li>
                        <li>OpenAPI to DITA</li>
                        <li>Confluence to DITA</li>
                        <li>DocBook to DITA</li>
                        <li>XML to JSON/YAML</li>
                        <li>JSON to XML</li>
                        <li>YAML to JSON/XML</li>
                        <li>JSON to YAML</li>
                    </ul>
                    <p>For more details see <a
                            href="https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/ug-editor/topics/batch-converter-addon.html"
                            >https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/ug-editor/topics/batch-converter-addon.html</a>
                    </p>
                </div>
                <hr/>
                <div class="whatsnew">
                    <h3>What's new in version 5.3.0</h3>
                    <ul>
                        <li>The Markdown to DITA conversion used by the Oxygen Batch Converter add-on was updated to be compatible with all enhancements made in version 5.5.0 of the org.lwdita DITA OT plugin.</li>
                        <li>Increased the minimum required version of Oxygen to 26.0.</li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
                <div>
                    <h3>What's new in version 5.2.0</h3>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <b>OpenAPI to DITA</b>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Fixed an issue where the OpenAPI to DITA conversion failed when the document contained the "*/*" MIME type.</li>
                                <li>Fixed invalid IDs on topics resulting from OpenAPI tags that contained multiple words separated by spaces.</li>
                                <li>Fixed a case where the description from responses was lost during the conversion of OpenAPI v2.</li>
                            </ul></li><li>
                                <b>Word to HTML/DITA</b>
                                <ul>
                                    <li>Added 'frame', 'rowsep', and 'colsep' attributes to tables from the resulting DITA documents.</li>
                                    <li>Fixed a case where the resulting tables had duplicate IDs.</li>
                                    <li>Added a default configuration for codeblocks in the Word Styles Mapping table.</li>
                                    <li>Fixed a case where the custom styles based on a normal style that didn't have a Word style mapping were not properly reported as unknown.</li>
                                </ul></li>
                        <li>
                            <b>Confluence to DITA</b>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Fixed an XSLT error that occurred when converting Confluence documents with duplicate IDs.</li>
                                <li>Removed queries from image paths. This prevents publishing errors caused by the presence of a query component in the URI.</li>
                            </ul></li>
                        <li>
                            <b>Others</b>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Updated the JTidy library to version 1.0.4.</li>
                                <li>Increased the minimum required version of Oxygen to 25.1.</li>
                                <li>Removed the Jackson libraries because these are already available in Oxygen.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
                <div>
                    <h3>What's new in version 5.1.0</h3>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Added two new conversions: <b>YAML to XML</b> and <b>XML to YAML</b>.</li>
                        <li>
                            <b>Word to HTML/DITA</b>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The processing of table captions was improved. The table is now obtained
                                    with a caption child in HTML or with a title in DITA. </li>
                                <li>The width of table columns is now preserved.</li>
                                <li> The processing of figure captions was improved. For XHTML, a
                                    <i>&lt;figure></i> element is obtained with a
                                    <i>&lt;figcaption></i> child element. For DITA, a
                                    <i>&lt;fig></i> element is obtained with a <i>&lt;title></i>
                                    child element. </li>
                                <li>The saving of images was improved and the name from the Word internal
                                    structure is preserved.</li>
                                <li>Fixed an issue where the content was incorrectly merged between two
                                    different unordered lists.</li>
                            </ul></li>
                        <li>
                            <b>Others</b>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Removed the SnakeYAML library because this is already available in Oxygen.</li>
                                <li>Increased the minimum required version of Oxygen to 23.1.</li>
                                <li>Removed some Flexmark Java Extension libraries that are not used when converting Markdown.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
                <div>
                    <h3>What's new in version 5.0.1</h3>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Fixed an issue with Word to HTML/DITA conversions where content was incorrectly merged between two different lists.</li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
                <div>
                    <h3>What's new in version 5.0.0</h3>
                    <ul>
                        <li><b>OpenAPI to DITA</b>
                            <ul>
                                <li>You can now convert JSON or YAML files that use and conform to the OpenAPI specification (versions 2.0, 3.0, or 3.1) to DITA documents and there is a 'Create DITA maps from OpenAPI documents' option that can be selected to instruct the converter to split the documents into separate topics that are referenced in a DITA map.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                        <li><b>Word to HTML/DITA</b>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Improved the Word styles mapping configuration by inheriting the style configuration of the custom style from the base style.</li>
                                <li>SVG images embedded in Word documents are preserved as SVG.</li>
                                <li>IDs that result from image and table bookmarks are now handled better to find the correct location.</li>
                                <li>Improved the IDs generation on topics and sections by using the text from headings.</li>
                                <li>Improved the handling of tables by preserving header row information during the conversion.</li>
                                <li>Fixed a case where a list that contains content between list items was broken into multiple lists.</li>
                                <li>Fixed a case where multiple ordered lists were merged into one.</li>
                                <li>Fixed a case where the conversion failed when the document contains duplicate mappings between numberings and styles.</li>
                                <li>Fixed a case where WMF images were not handled by the converter.</li>
                                <li>Fixed a case where the DITA result contained an invalid MathML equation.</li>
                                <li>Fixed a case where the DITA result contained images wrapped in the 'b' element.</li>
                                <li>Fixed a case where the value edited in the Word Styles Mapping table from the preferences page was not saved.</li>
                                <li>Updated the Java-Mammoth library used for Word to HTML/DITA conversions to version 1.5.0.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                        <li><b>HTML to DITA</b>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Improved the conversion of object elements from HTML by adding a proper 'outputclass' attribute in the DITA result.</li>
                                <li>Added an option in the conversion dialog box that allows you to decide whether or not the 'div' elements will be ignored.</li>
                                <li>Fixed a case where 'id' and 'class' attributes were lost when breaking paragraphs by processing the 'br' elements.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                        <li><b>Markdown to DITA</b>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Added support for the Markdown abbreviations.</li>
                                <li>Improved the handling of the local references.</li>
                                <li>Improved the conversion to allow processing of headings specified as HTML in the Markdown documents.</li>
                                <li>Improved the handling of the HTML anchor elements in the Markdown documents.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                        <li><b>Others</b>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The formatting of 'pre' elements are prevented when converting HTML to XHTML.</li>
                                <li>Fixed the layout of the preferences page because it was not entirely visible on low resolution screens.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
                <div>
                    <h3>What's new in version 4.0.0</h3>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Added a Confluence to DITA conversion.</li>
                        <li>Added a DocBook to DITA conversion.</li>
                        <li>Improved the name of the extracted DITA topic files when converting to a DITA map with topics.</li>
                        <li>Improved the title extraction of the DITA map when converting to a DITA map with topics.</li>
                        <li>The 'alt' attributes from images are now handled properly when converting HTML to DITA.</li>
                    </ol>
                </div>
                <div>
                    <h3>What's new in version 3.2.1</h3>
                    <ol>
                        <li><b>Critical/Security:</b> The add-on no longer distributes Apache Log4j
                            libraries to avoid the Log4Shell exploit. For more info see: <a
                                href="https://www.randori.com/blog/cve-2021-44228/"
                                >CVE-2021-44228</a>.</li>
                        <li>Audio, video, picture, object, and iframe elements are handled when
                            converting HTML to DITA.</li>
                        <li>Fixed a case where the table of contents was not ignored when converting
                            Word to DITA.</li>
                    </ol>
                </div>
                <div>
                    <h3>What's new in version 3.2.0</h3>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Added a preferences page that contains: <ul>
                                <li>An option for customizing the conversions from Word (Word to
                                    HTML/DITA/DocBook) by mapping Word styles to HTML elements.</li>
                                <li>Added an option for choosing the maximum heading level for
                                    creating nested topics or separate DITA topic files when
                                    converting Word/HTML to DITA.</li>
                            </ul></li>
                        <li>Warnings are now presented if unrecognized Word styles are found when
                            converting Word documents.</li>
                        <li>Improved the hierarchy level obtained in conversions from Word/HTML to
                            DITA maps.</li>
                        <li>All '<i>class</i>' attributes are converted from the intermediary HTML
                            into DITA '<i>outputclass</i>' attributes when processing Word to
                            DITA.</li>
                        <li>Added an '<i>outputclass</i>' attribute with an "<i>endnote</i>" value
                            on the '<i>fn</i>' DITA elements that resulted from Word endnotes.</li>
                        <li>The file name is used as the title when the document doesn't contain
                            headings in Word/HTML to DITA conversions.</li>
                        <li>The table of contents is ignored when converting Word to HTML/DITA.</li>
                        <li>Copied relative resources into the output folder in HTML to DITA
                            conversions.</li>
                        <li>Superscript and subscript are allowed when converting Markdown to
                            DITA.</li>
                        <li>Fixed some cases where internal references were not converted properly
                            in Word to HTML/DITA conversions.</li>
                        <li>Fixed a case where equations were not converted in Word to HTML/DITA
                            conversions.</li>
                        <li>Fixed an issue where a space between underline elements and other inline
                            elements was ignored.</li>
                        <li>Fixed an error in HTML to XHTML conversions when processing elements
                            with whitespace content.</li>
                    </ol>
                </div>
                <div>
                    <h3>What's new in version 3.1.0</h3>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Cross-references are now handled properly when converting Word to
                            HTML/DITA.</li>
                        <li>Index entries, footnotes and endnotes are now handled properly when
                            converting Word to DITA.</li>
                        <li>References to local HTML documents are now automatically updated when
                            converting HTML to DITA.</li>
                        <li>Fixed an issue with HTML to DITA/DocBook conversions where extra new
                            lines were added when converting "pre" elements.</li>
                        <li>Fixed an issue with Excel to DITA conversions that sometimes resulted in
                            table elements with invalid IDs (<a
                                href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/oxygen-resources-converter/issues/51"
                                >#51</a>).</li>
                        <li>Fixed an issue with Word/HTML to DITA/DocBook conversions that caused
                            spaces between inline elements to be removed.</li>
                        <li>Updated the Java Mammoth library to version 1.4.2.</li>
                        <li>Updated the jTidy library to version 1.0.2.</li>
                    </ol>
                </div>
                <div>
                    <h3>What's new in version 3.0.0</h3>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Added two new conversions: <b>YAML to JSON</b> and <b>JSON to
                            YAML</b>.</li>
                        <li>Added import actions to the <i>Append child</i>, <i>Insert Before</i>,
                            and <i>Insert After</i> sub-menus from the DITA Maps Manager's
                            contextual menu. They convert documents and automatically insert them in
                            the DITA map.</li>
                        <li>Added the converter actions to the <i>File->Import/Convert->Additional
                                conversions</i> sub-menu.</li>
                        <li>Re-organized the converter actions for easier access.</li>
                    </ol>
                </div>
                <div>
                    <h3>What's new in version 2.1.0</h3>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Added a new option for converting Markdown documents with multiple
                            headings into <b>DITA maps with referenced DITA topics</b> (Markdown to
                            DITA).</li>
                        <li>Added a new option for creating DITA <i>short description</i> elements
                            in the Markdown to DITA conversion.</li>
                        <li>Improved the Markdown to DITA conversion to allow conversions of
                            documents that start with a high heading level or increase the heading
                            level with more than one unit.</li>
                        <li>Added a new option for converting HTML documents with multiple headings
                            into <b>DITA maps with referenced DITA topics</b>(HTML to DITA).</li>
                        <li>Fixed various small bugs in the HTML to DITA and Word to DITA
                            conversions.</li>
                    </ol>
                </div>
            </body>
        </html>
    </xt:description>
    <xt:license><![CDATA[
        Copyright 2018 Syncro Soft SRL

   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
   you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
   You may obtain a copy of the License at

       http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
   limitations under the License.

The Plugin may include certain of the following third party software components. 
The copyright notices, disclaimers and license terms applicable to such third party software components are listed below:

oxygen-patched-lwdita-for-batch-converter
Patch for Lightweight DITA for DITA-OT library.
Site: https://github.com/jelovirt/org.lwdita 
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

oxygen-patched-mammoth-for-batch-converter
Patch for Java Mammoth library.
Site: https://github.com/mwilliamson/java-mammoth
License: BSD 2-Clause "Simplified" License ( https://raw.githubusercontent.com/mwilliamson/java-mammoth/master/LICENSE)

oxygen-patched-jtidy-for-batch-converter
Patch for JTidy library.
Site: https://github.com/jtidy/jtidy
License: Java HTML Tidy - JTidy License ( https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jtidy/jtidy/master/LICENSE.txt)

]]></xt:license>
</xt:extension>
