<!-- This is used to install the plugin as an add-on:
https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/versions/18.1/ug-editor/topics/packing-and-deploying-addons.html#packing-and-deploying-addons
 -->
<xt:extensions xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension/extensions.xsd">
    <xt:extension xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
        id="com.oxygenxml.resources.batch.converter.plugin">
        <xt:location   href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/oxygen-resources-convertor/releases/download/3.1.0/oxygen-batch-converter-3.1.0-plugin.jar"/>
        <xt:version>3.1.0</xt:version>
        <xt:oxy_version>20.0+</xt:oxy_version>
        <xt:type>plugin</xt:type>
        <xt:author>Syncro Soft</xt:author>
        <xt:name>Batch Documents Converter</xt:name>
        <xt:description><html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
            <head>
                <title>Oxygen resources converter</title>
            </head>
            <body>
                <div>
                    <p>This add-on contributes actions in the Tools menu and contextual menu to enable batch conversion between various formats: 
                    </p>
                    	<ul>
                    		<li>HTML to XHTML/DITA/DocBook</li>
                    		<li>Markdown to XHTML/DITA/DocBook</li>
                    		<li>XML to JSON</li>
                    		<li>JSON to XML</li>
                    		<li>Excel to DITA</li>
                    		<li>Word to XHTML/DITA/DocBook</li>
                    	</ul>
                    <p>For more details see <a
                        href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/oxygen-resources-convertor"
                        >https://github.com/oxygenxml/oxygen-resources-convertor</a>
                    </p>
                </div>
                <hr/>
                <div>
                    <h3>What's new in version 3.1.0</h3>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Cross-references are now handled properly when converting Word to HTML/DITA.</li>
                        <li>Index entries, footnotes and endnotes are now handled properly when converting Word to DITA.</li>
                        <li>References to local HTML documents are now automatically updated when converting HTML to DITA.</li>
                        <li>Fixed an issue with HTML to DITA conversions where extra new lines were added when converting "pre" elements.</li>
                        <li>Fixed an issue with Excel to DITA conversions that sometimes resulted in table elements with invalid IDs (<a href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/oxygen-resources-converter/issues/51">#51</a>).</li>
                        <li>Fixed an issue with Word/HTML to DITA conversions that caused spaces between inline elements to be removed.</li>
                        <li>Updated the Java Mammoth library to version 1.4.2.</li>
                        <li>Updated the jTidy library to version 1.0.2.</li>
                    </ol>
                </div>
                <div>
                    <h3>What's new in version 3.0.0</h3>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Added two new conversions: YAML to JSON and JSON to YAML.</li>
                        <li>Added import actions to the "Append child", "Insert Before", and "Insert After" sub-menus from the DITA Maps Manager's contextual menu. They convert documents and automatically insert them in the DITA map.</li>
                        <li>Added the converter actions to the "File->Import/Convert->Additional conversions" sub-menu.</li>
                        <li>Re-organized the converter actions for easier access.</li>
                    </ol>
                </div>
                <div>
					<h3>What's new in version 2.1.0</h3>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Added a new option for converting Markdown documents with multiple headings into <b>DITA maps with referenced DITA topics</b> (Markdown to DITA).</li>
                        <li>Added a new option for creating DITA <i>short description</i> elements in the Markdown to DITA conversion.</li>
                        <li>Improved the Markdown to DITA conversion to allow conversions of documents that start with a high heading level or increase the heading level with more than one unit.</li>
                        <li>Added a new option for converting HTML documents with multiple headings into <b>DITA maps with referenced DITA topics</b>(HTML to DITA).</li>
                        <li>Fixed various small bugs in the HTML to DITA and Word to DITA conversions.</li>
                    </ol>
                </div>
            </body>
        </html>
        </xt:description>
        <xt:license><![CDATA[
        Copyright 2018 Syncro Soft SRL

   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
   you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
   You may obtain a copy of the License at

       http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
   limitations under the License.

The Plugin may include certain of the following third party software components. 
The copyright notices, disclaimers and license terms applicable to such third party software components are listed below:

oxygen-patched-lwdita-for-batch-converter-24.0-SNAPSHOT.jar
Patch for Lightweight DITA for DITA-OT library.
Site: https://github.com/jelovirt/org.lwdita 
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

oxygen-patched-mammoth-for-batch-converter-24.0-SNAPSHOT.jar
Patch for Java Mammoth library.
Site: https://github.com/mwilliamson/java-mammoth
License: BSD 2-Clause "Simplified" License ( https://raw.githubusercontent.com/mwilliamson/java-mammoth/master/LICENSE)

oxygen-patched-jtidy-for-batch-converter-24.0-SNAPSHOT.jar
Patch for JTidy library.
Site: https://github.com/jtidy/jtidy
License: Java HTML Tidy - JTidy License ( https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jtidy/jtidy/master/LICENSE.txt)

]]></xt:license>
    </xt:extension>
</xt:extensions>
